latinstockinvesting.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy | ACAMAR GLOBAL INVESTMENTS

### Our Commitment to Privacy

Acamar Global Investments is committed to maintaining the confidentiality, integrity, and security of personal information about our current and prospective customers. Please note that certain details of this policy may depend on whether you deal with us through an investment professional, directly as an individual investor, or whether Acamar Global provides services to your employer or plan sponsor. The privacy policies of Acamar Global Investments is reviewed annually. Our printed and online notices are then updated to reflect any changes.

**Acamar Global Investments Privacy Policy**

**How and why we obtain personal information**  
Acamar Global takes great care to protect personal information about you and when we use it, we do so with respect for your privacy. We may use personal information about you to service and maintain your account; process transactions in your account; respond to inquiries from you or your representative; develop, offer, and deliver products and services; or to fulfill legal and regulatory requirements. Acamar Global may collect public and non-public personal information about you from any of the following sources:

• You or your representative on applications or forms (for example, name, address, Social Security number, birth date, assets and income)  
• You or your employer or plan sponsor if Acamar Global provides them with recordkeeping services (for example, payroll, human resources, or benefits information)  
• Transactional activity in your account (for example, trading history and balances)  
• Other interactions with Acamar Global (for example, discussions with our customer service staff or information you enter into our websites)  
• Information from consumer reporting agencies (for example, to assess your creditworthiness for margin products)  
• Information from other third-party data services (for example, to verify your identity and to better understand your product and service needs)  
• You or your representative regarding your preferences (for example, your choice of electronic statement delivery, or the screen layout you specify if you use our Internet sites)  
• Other sources with your consent or with the consent of your representative (for example, from other institutions if you transfer positions into Acamar Global)

**How we protect information about you**

Acamar Global considers the protection of personal information to be a foundation of customer trust and a sound business practice. We employ physical, electronic and procedural controls and we regularly adapt these controls to respond to changing requirements and advances in technology. At Acamar Global, we restrict access to personal information to those who require it to develop, support, offer and deliver products and services to you.

**How we share information about you with third parties**

Acamar Global does not share personal information about our customers with unaffiliated third parties for use in marketing their products and services. We may share personal information with the following entities:

• Unaffiliated service providers (for example, printing and mailing companies, securities clearinghouses, marketing service providers, and other entities who may provide services at Acamar Global's direction)  
• Government agencies, other regulatory bodies and law enforcement officials (for example, for tax purposes or for reporting suspicious transactions)  
• Other organizations, with your consent or as directed by your representative (for example, if you use Acamar Global as a financial reference in applying for credit with another institution), or as permitted or required by law (for example, for fraud prevention)

Our service providers are obligated to keep the personal information we share with them confidential and use it only to provide services specified by Acamar Global. 

Based on the nature of your relationship with Acamar Global, we may exchange information with other third parties as described below:

• If Acamar Global provides workplace services to your employer or plan sponsor, such as payroll, human resources or benefits recordkeeping services, Acamar Global may exchange any information received in connection with such services with your employer or plan sponsor or others they may authorize.  
• If you conduct business with Acamar Global through your investment professional, we may exchange information we collect with your investment professional or with others they may authorize.

**Privacy online**

Privacy, security, and service in Acamar Global's online operations are just as critical as in the rest of our business. We use firewall barriers, encryption techniques and authentication procedures, among others, to maintain the security of your online session and to protect Acamar Global accounts and systems from unauthorized access.  
When you interact with us through online channels (for example, websites and mobile applications) owned and controlled by Acamar Global Investments ("Acamar Global websites"), Acamar Global manages personal information in accordance with all of the practices and safeguards described previously. When you visit Acamar Global websites, we may collect technical and navigational information, such as device type, browser type, Internet protocol address, pages visited, and average time spent on Acamar Global websites. We use this information for a variety of purposes, such as maintaining the security of your online session, facilitating site navigation, improving Acamar Global website design and functionality, and personalizing your experience on Acamar Global websites. Additionally, the following policies and practices apply when you are online.

**Cookies and similar technologies**

We use cookies and similar technologies to support the operation of Acamar Global websites. Cookies are small amounts of data that a website sends to a web browser on a visitor's computer. Our cookies help us to collect information about visitors to Acamar Global websites, including date and time of visits, pages viewed, amount of time spent on our sites, or general information about the device used to access the site. Acamar Global cookies are also used for security purposes and to personalize your experience, such as customizing your screen layout. You can refuse or delete cookies. Most browsers and mobile devices offer their own settings to manage cookies. If you refuse a cookie when on an Acamar Global website, or if you delete cookies, you may experience some inconvenience in your use of Acamar Global websites. For example, you may not be able to sign in and access your account, or we may not be able to recognize you, your device, or your online preferences. Both Acamar Global and third-party service providers we hire may use cookies and other technologies, such as web beacons or pixel tags, in online advertising as described below. We do not share personally identifiable information about our customers with these third-party service providers, and these service providers do not collect such information on our behalf.

**Advertising on non-Acamar Global websites**

Acamar Global also advertises our products and services on websites not affiliated with Acamar Global. We contract with third-party advertising companies to display these ads, and they may use cookies and similar technologies to optimize the placement of our ads. We do not permit these companies to use information they collect on Acamar Global's behalf for any purpose other than to assist them with advertising Acamar Global products and services. When we hire third-party online advertising companies, they may provide you with Acamar Global advertisements that may be relevant to your interests, as determined by your activity on Acamar Global and non-Acamar Global websites. Such advertisements are known as "interest-based advertisements." You may opt-out of receiving interest-based advertisements from online advertising companies by clicking on the AdChoices icon (which appears on all Acamar Global interest-based ads) and following the opt-out instructions. For more information about interest-based advertising please see <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp> .

**Connecting with Acamar Global on social media sites**

Acamar Global provides experiences on social media platforms that enable online sharing and collaboration among users who have registered to use them. We may collect information you provide by interacting with us via social media, such as photographs, opinions, or Twitter handle. Any content you post, such as pictures, information, opinions, or any personal information that you make available to other participants on these social platforms, is also subject to the terms of use and privacy policies of those platforms. Please refer to them to better understand your rights and obligations with regard to such content.

**Protecting children's privacy online**

Acamar Global websites are not directed to individuals under the age of thirteen (13). Acamar Global does not intentionally collect information on Acamar Global websites from those we actually know are under 13, and we request that these individuals do not provide personal information through the sites.

**Additional information**

If you are a former customer, these policies also apply to you; we treat your information with the same care as we do information about current customers.  
Acamar Global offers several options for accessing and, if necessary, correcting your account information. You can review your information using your statements, or through our automated telephone or Internet services. You may also write or call us with your request for information. If we serve you through an investment professional, please contact them directly. Specific Internet addresses, mailing addresses and telephone numbers are listed on your statements and other correspondence.
